10th Day Living Together
We're back!
Some perv was staring at my tits on the train today. It was so creepy.
Can I let off some steam with ya?
Well, I'm gonna anyways.
You like titty-fucks, don'tcha, Otaku-kun?
Look at his face, it's, like, super obvious!
Look at that titty-fuck face he's making!
He probly thinks about titty-fucking all the time!
Defs! He stares at our tits all the time!
Oh my, you're thrusting your hips so hard.
Hilarious. Otaku-kun really loves titty-fucks. We gotta do it again sometime.
Oh geez, his dick is rubbing against my nipples.
Your dick's getting, like, super hot.
What? Are you going to cum?
Amazing, it's, like, shooting so far!
Fuck'n hilarious, that's, like, way too much.
I'm back!
Oh, the titty-fuck queen's back.
We found out Otaku-kun really loves titty-fucks.
Ahh! Let me join in too!
Incredible, your dick's burning hot.
Ah, looksies, your dick's, like, completely sandwiched.
Ah, so good.
Right? My titjobs are the best, right?
Ah, I'm cu–
Huh? Cummin' already?
Not allowed, that's too fast. Hold it in a bit longer.
Cumming!
That was way too fast.
But your cum's, like, so thick!
You're, like, amazing, mister.
Invasion!
Busty
GalHarem
Life
Invasion!
Busty
Life
GalHarem
Busty
Life
GalHarem
14th Day Living Together
Ah, so this is what Otaku-kun likes to look at.
Ah... um... actually... that's...
Oh, another panty shot.
Seriously? This is what otakus fap to?
Oh, I know! Hey, Otaku-kun!
How's this for a panty shot?!
Ah, so super cute!
Super sexy time panties!
Check it out, you can see my pussy through em!
Take a close look at my panties!
You can sniffy sniff them all you want!
Stop trying to be so cutesy. It's kinda creepy.
Huh?! I'm, like, always acting like this!
'Sides, Otaku-kun's, like, completely hooked!
POTATO CHIPS
I'll sit on your face. Lie down.
You're really gettin' into this!
Now stick your tongue into my pussy and lick, come on!
Ayane, like, really loves face-sitting, ya'know?
It's the same for Otaku-kun! Just look how hard he is!
Heh, you're getting this hard when a girl sits on your face?
What a pervert!
He's so gentle when he licks me.
Too cute!
Oh, Otaku-kun may make a good doggie.
So much precum.
Huh, are you going to cum?
Are you gonna cum while I smush you with my pussy?!
Does the cute little doggie want to cum?! Then 'woof' for me if you want to cum!
Woof!
That felt sooo good!
I can't believe he actually barked. Hilarious.
He really turned into a dog!
Hey, cum till you're empty!
W-Wa–... I-I can't...
You can do it!
Spray! Spray it all out!
Cum– Cummin– CUMMING!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
Take this!
He came!
His expression is too cute.
Crazy, he really came! His face is, like, so red!
His dick turned red too.
Huh? Wanna go again?
Just kidding.
Huh?
Good morning Mister.
You were totes amazing yesterday.
But this is a bit embarrassing,
standing here with no makeup.
N-Not at all... you're incredibly cute...
For real?!
I'm so happy. I'm falling in love with you. Let's kiss.
Your dick's, like, always so hard, mister. It's pressing tight between my thighs!
My pussy's already getting wet.
We don't have any condoms. So how 'bout you grind against my pussy all you want!
French kissing and grinding together while I don't have makeup on... It's like we're lovers...
Ahh... Cumming!
Not yet!
If you're going to cum, wait till we're in bed.
But I want a dick so bad right now... ahh, I totally can't resist!
Come on, stick it in! It's fine even without a condom.
Look, look.
Impressive, right? I used to do gymnastics.
But... bareback...
Stop worrying, and stick it in! Hurry, hurry.
Ah, it's in!
So hot!
It feels even hotter without a condom, right?
Maybe it's, like, 'cause of my body heat.
Go deeper! Ah, so good... my pussy's totally sucking you in!
I'm... going to cum.
That's too quick.
You have to resist!
Seriously, you're getting so rough!
I love it! Thrust even harder, yes!
I'm cumming!
Ooh... I'm so happy!
Hey~ Who said you could cum inside me?
You came so much.
You're finally out! That took forever. Did'ya do it?
I let Mister cum inside me for fun!
Seriously?!
It felt super good.
Ah, not fair, not fair.
You can probably cum again, right? I want it too!
Don't totally drain him. Save some for me.
What? Just give it all to me!
Time to get a taste of this raw cock!
Does it feel good bareback?
I'm absolutely lovin' this!
Your dick's rubbing my pussy like crazy!
You can cum inside.
Your swimmers are, like, probably weak anyways.
Go ahead and shoot them all inside me.
Oh, you're fondling my tits now? You're gettin' pretty serious!
I'm gonna squeeze you with my pussy so tight... you won't even be able to pull out.
Ah! My nipples... I love this! Don't stop!
It feels so good. Keep teasing my nipples!
I'm cumming!
Ahh yes, so good... Look me in the eyes...
Your dick's trembling so much. Too cute!
Haha, we fucked like a real couple!
Hey now, this isn't the time to rest.
My pussy's already so wet. I'm gonna ride you hard.
Hey, how does Reina's pussy feel?
Like, totally good, right?
So good!
You get to have raw sex with us now. What a luxury.
And to think, Otaku-kun was a virgin before.
We're gonna train you to be our pet.
So hard... The tip's scraping against my pussy walls.
This is... so good!
I'm going to cum.
You're going to cum?
When you're thrusting so deep? What are you gonna do if I get pregnant?
I-I'll take responsibility.
Are you proposing to me? You're so funny!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Like I'd have a kid with a loser like you, idiot!
I'm cumming
It's here!
Don't pull away. You can still cum, right? Come on.
Nice, you came so much.
Hey, everyone did it raw? I wanna turn too.
How 'bout we just skip class today and fuck all day?
Let's totally do that!
You can still keep going, right, Mister? Let's continue.
Not fair. I wanna do it raw too.
Wait, I'm going to take a shower. Just a sec.
Otaku-kun, before I get back, you have to hold it in!
Ha? Then I'll make him cum in one second.
Feelin' tired? Want to suck on my boobs?
You're licking so desperately. So cute.
Ha, I feel like it's already coming out.
Don't hold back. Just cum!
More subs at AmateurSubs.com
I'm going to defeat you with my boobs.
Feelin' good?
Your nipples are so sensitive. Are you a girl?
Cum!
Cum, cum, cum!
Ah... He actually came.
Hey, why did you cum? Resist more!
Even though his dick is weak, it recovers quickly.
Haha, suck, suck.
Ha, you're completely sandwiched.
Are Lilia's boobs that delicious?
Oh, my nipples got hard.
Ah, amazing. I love this. So good.
I haven't had raw sex in a long while.
Lilia's pussy... is so amazingly tight.
I love the way you say that.
I-I'm cumming...
Do it... creampie me!
So hot... getting a creampie feels great!
I can't type like this, don't shake me so much.
Just hurry and let it all out.
Oh yeah! Let's take a picture while we're having sex.
Send that to me later!
No probs!
Next is my turn.
Oh shit!
I'm, like, super feeling it!  Your dick feels so good, mister!
This position is even better! You're so hard. It's hitting all the right spots!
Oh no, my hips won't stop moving.
Lilia you're kissing him so hard.  I've, like, never seen you do that!
French kissing is so amazing.
I wanna French kiss him too!
Taking it from behind looks awesome! I'll do that next!
Ah! I-I'm cumming!
I'm gonna be filled with cum again.  You're, like, seriously gonna get me pregnant!  Let it all out!
Ah! Getting fucked from behind feels so fucking good!
Thrust your hips harder! Come on!
She's moaning so loud.
Ayane totally loves getting fucked doggy style.
You're really lovin' kissing him, Reina.
I think I'm fallin' for Otaku-kun.
I think we've all fallen in love with mister.
His reactions are way too cute. It's so much fun to have sex with him!
Let it all out!
Can't hold it? Go ahead and fill'er up!
You're gonna cum a lot again this time, right? I wanna watch you cum!
You came so much. Crazy!
Seeing you cum so much makes me want to fuck again. You can go again, right?
Ah... so good, so good.
You're completely drained right?
Oh, I just got paid.
Yay!
Welp, we'll be going back.
Let's do it again some time.
Sorry to bother you for these two weeks.
We had a great time.
Cya!
Let's do it again!
Brought to you by AmateurSubs!
Translation: Folles
Proofreading: dusty
Timing: doplank
Typesetting: LR
QC: Oceania