Team Beast!
Who are you?
Get ready!
Holy Jewel, Saint Change!
The sacred light that destroys evil!
The Holy Crystal Flower, Saint
Lime, has arrived in the name of justice!
Is she a Magic Girl?
It's bad! Run!
I won't let you get away!
Saint...
... Penetrator!
Saint Cherry...
Onii-chan, where have you been?
Seihou Shouka Saint Lime
Episode 1: The Sacred Crystal
Flower, Saint Lime, has
arrived in the name of justice!
One night, the Heroic Branch began Operation:
Move from "Majin Crystal" to Headquarters...
We already know you're
transporting the Majin Crystal.
Give me that crystal to me with no word,
Devil Beetle, High Command Beast Forces.
Right, the Majin Crystal will turn
Beetle-sama into a powerful majin!
A suspicious light that obeys evil.
The Lewd Flower, Bloody Cherry!
I came for my master!
I found you!
I won't allow it!
Get out of the way, Onii-chan! I can't kill him!
Huh? Is it possible you're... Hina?
Cherry, do you know this woman?
Yes, master.
She's my younger sister, Sakurai Hina.
Devil Beetle!
Because of you, my Onii-chan...!
The beautiful and perfect Saint Cherry is like this!
Your sin must be punished with death...!
W-Why? Stop, Onii-chan!
I see, you've become a Magic Girl, too.
You're so cute, you look like me...
These big breasts are also to my master's liking.
O-Onii-chan, what are you saying...?
Well, it's time...
...of the punishment you've waited so long for!
N-No! Onii-chan, why are you touching my breasts?
Why, you say?
So that my master can easily enter you, Lime.
You're feeling it with your
breasts right away. No! No!
Besides, my master will rape
this place with his splendid penis.
So I have to relax you.
No! No! Onii-chan!
Saint Lime, your eroticism has made me this!
W-What's that?
The master's penis always looks
awesome and makes me tremble!
Why am I stuck with my eyesight
and with my heart pumping?
S-Stop, my virginity is only for Onii-chan!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you, no doubt!
You pervert scumbag!
You still pretend to be strong
even if you're suffering, well done!
D-Don't pinch me, asshole!
No!
What's this? No! No!
Don't rub it like that!
Didn't you just insult my Beetle-sama before?
This is your punishment.
W-Why? It should hurt to
penetrate, why does it feel so good?
You must be confused, right?
The scent and body fluids of
Beetle-sama can excite women.
And with his penis, it will be even more pleasant!
You'll soon have an orgasm like a whore, Lime!
I don't want to get excited for this person!
Don't hit me inside!
Come on, give the mercyless blow to Lime, master!
His penis gets bigger and bigger!
No! No! No! If you do that, I...!
D-Damn you! I'll kill you no matter what!
This is the Sacred Crystal
Light of Magic Girl, isn't it?
Cherry!
This heat is from my Onii-chan!
There's no other choice... everyone, retreat!
Don't run away, you coward!
My vagina still... That bastard!
Damn it!
Saint Lime Grade of Modification 12%
I found it! It's this one! Cherry's
Porn Website Cherry's porn website.
I hope there's information about the
Beast Army and my Onii-chan here.
This... no doubt, it's Onii-chan!
Although I don't want to see Onii-chan like this...
B-But who knows when information
about Onii-chan will appear...
I have to take a good look!
Finally, it's time for the announcement!
This is a newly opened place by Beetle-sama.
We're looking for a masochistic, perverted actress!
This is it!
I can help Cherry by sneaking in!
We'll be waiting for you!
When I find Beetle, I'll transform
and attack him. One day at 6:00 p.m.
Sakurai Hina uses costume magic to sneak into a
Beetle-owned Show Pub. Then I'll immobilize Cherry.
Don't worry, as long as I have
the power of my Onii-chan...
This is...
Welcome, I was waiting for you!
Come on, hurry up!
Beetle-sama is eager to prove you!
So this is Devil Beetle!
Holy Jewel, Saint Change!
The sacred light that destroys evil!
The Sacred Crystal Flower, Saint Lime, has arrived!
Get ready!
Why is my body shaking all of a sudden?
This smoke is made from our body
fluids and has an aphrodisiac effect.
I'm gonna taste that body right away.
Let me control Lime's body.
Come on! Move, move!
W-Why my butt is...? No, stop!
I don't want to do this!
First, I'll give love to this lewd ass!
Take this!
Even though Cherry controls
her, I can't let my guard down.
It's not that I'm afraid of you, you know?
If your moans are so strong,
you're obviously enjoying it, Lime.
You've already become a
promiscuous girl, haven't you, Lime?
T-That's not true! There!
I noticed, you haven't stopped looking at
the master's penis in a while, have you?
Oh, for your reaction, it seems that's enough.
That's why...
It's time for the penetration session!
I came! I've cum, don't keep hitting me!
You seem to enjoy it a lot!
Well, after you feel the master's penis,
it's normal that you become like this.
You can't forget that, can you?
The semen.
Semen?
You want that thick, hot liquid to
fill your masochistic womb, right?
I don't want it! That's not true!
His penis is getting bigger and hotter inside!
No! I still remember, so I know!
This big, hard penis...
Yeah, he's gonna give me a lot of his semen!
I'm cumming, Lime!
No! I'm cumming! I'm still cumming!
This isn't over!
Don't thrust while spanking me!
Stop!
If your penis keeps hitting me...
I...!
Although I don't control you anymore...
...your hips move like this.
So, speak like a whore and say: "Your
penis feels so good" while you cum!
Cherry is right, I'm moving on my own!
This splendid penis melts my head and vagina!
It feels good!
I can't resist anymore!
Your penis...! Your penis feels
so good when you thrust it in me!
Take this! You like it, don't you?
Yeah, I like this!
Getting your penis deep inside all the way to
my womb while you spank me, feels so good!
Since you've become a whore...
As a gift, I'm gonna give you a creampie!
Do it...! Your penis is going
to release semen again...!
Cumming until faint and pee yourself,
there's no doubt both are family.
The lab is ready to work
After this, you will brainwash just like me.
Lime, from here you're going
to feel more and more pleasure.
So, wait and see.
Upscale: hstream.moe