My name is Kazu Notus, a biology graduate student.
My grandfather once said that in this world,
a race distinct from elves called "lewd elves" exists.
Nobody believed it but I'll definitely find them!
Ah...
U-Uhh, where am I?
Huh?
Hey, are you alright?
Whoa...
By any chance, are you a human!?
The Lewd Elf
Search Records
Her name is Mana. Based on what she said,
she's unmistakably one of those lewd elves!
I couldn't be any luckier!
Mana, about the way you're dressed...
My clothes? Is anything wrong with them?
My mom and older sister dress the same way.
I see, that's their traditional clothing...
I think it looks very nice on you.
Yay, thanks!
Ahh! Please don't jump around too much!
As I taught her various stuff while walking in the forest,
she started to call me "sensei".
Sensei, something has been troubling me...
Will you hear me out?
Sure, what is it?
You see, it's about the tips of my boobies.
They seem different from my sister's...
I wonder why...
U-Umm... Well, that would be...
I'm begging you, sensei! Tell me if you know!
Is there something wrong with me?
Oh no, she really is troubled about it!
If I don't answer her properly now,
I don't deserve to be called "sensei"!
You see, the tips of your breasts are just a little bit shy.
Huuuh?
So if we stimulate them like this...
I-It kinda feels weird...
I feel fuzzy...
Look, they came out.
Y-Yes...
Next, we do this on them...
S-Sensei, I love it when you stroke the tips!
My breasts get tingly and they feel good!
Sensei... K-Keep going...
O-Okay, that would be enough!
Ehh...
You already saw that the tips
are in there so it's all good.
Yeah...
Ahh, that was close... Any further and I might lose myself.
But since then...
Hey, sensei! Do that to my boobies again!
A-Again?
W-Well, the tips go back in right away...
Ahhhhh! I really love this!
Oh no, if this goes on...
Sensei, there's another thing I don't
understand. Will you hear me out?
Wh-What is it?
When you do this to my boobies,
my crotch starts to get wet.
It's not pee... I wonder what it is.
Oh, this stuff is naturally released when you feel good.
There's nothing weird about it.
Ehh... So, that's how it works...
Then, sensei...
Does this part of me have a weird shape or not?
N-No, it looks totally normal...
Uhhhh...
Are you okay, sensei? Are you not feeling well?
I-It's nothing, don't worry.
Drink this, sensei.
Okay, thanks. What's this?
My mom said that drinking it will make you lively.
D-Did she mean "lively" in that kind of sense!?
Whoa...
Sensei, what happened down here!?
Th-This is nothing!
It's swelling a lot! Let's get it out of there quickly!
Wait!
Whoa... This thing...
Sensei, your thing down here is different from mine.
This is kinda... I'm not really sure...
Like this? Will it shrink down if I do this?
Y-Yes, that's right...
Stroke it while wrapping your hands around it.
Ooh, I'm making her do something really bad!
Sensei, are you alright?
I-I'm okay...
Ah, no... Shit!
Wh-What is this gooey stuff? It smells weird...
But I wonder why my tummy is throbbing...
Sensei, my crotch feels strange...
Sensei, what are you doing?
W-Well, this is... That's it! This is a treatment!
Okay, I understand!
Please do it, sensei!
She believes me with such a pure heart!
I must help this girl right away!
S-Sensei, you went into my tummy!
A-Are you alright?
Yes... For some reason...
My tummy feels fuzzy!
Shit, it feels way too good inside her!
Sensei, my crotch feels good!
Do it harder!
Sensei's thing feels amazing!
It's thick and hard!
What is this thing called?
It's called a dick.
A dick...
Sensei's dick...
...feels good!
Your dick feels good!
Sensei, teasing my boobies at the same time...
...makes me feel even better!
Here it is... I feel something coming!
Shit, I ended up coming inside her...
Did you feel good, sensei?
It felt very good to me.
Hey, sensei...
Do it one more time!
Sensei, I like looking at your face while doing this!
S-Sensei! Sensei!
Please, sensei...
Let me have more of your hot stuff in my tummy!
Make it spurt out!
Sensei, thank you...
It feels so good... I'm so happy!
You bastard... What are you doing to my little sister!?
Oh, onee-chan!
Welcome home!
Uh-huh, I see...
You're saying that guy was not
being forcibly rough on you, then?
That's right! Hmmph!
Umm, can you untie me now?
Well, my little sister seems to be close to you.
There isn't any sign of her being harmed as well.
I'll let you off this time.
I am Tieru, Mana's older sister.
We've both been living here for a while now.
I'm Kazu, a biologist.
Mana happened to save me and here I am now...
And you went as far as having sex with her...
Biologists sure are something, huh?
To be honest, I was planning to present my research
on lewd elves at an academic
conference but I changed my mind.
Ohh? Why?
She is such a pure and genuine girl.
If the public ever sees her, she'll most
likely be preyed upon right away.
That's why I decided to keep my knowledge
about lewd elves within me.
I see...
That was a close call! You would've died
if you said anything uncalled for!
I-Is that so!?
The thing about us lewd elves
is that we struggle a lot in reproduction.
That's why procreative sex is an essential task for us.
If Mana willingly chose you as her partner,
I have nothing much else to say.
But since you laid your hands on her,
you should take responsibility!
R-Responsibility?
I'm telling you to keep it up until you get her pregnant!
Hey, Mana... Don't do that...
Why? Look at your dick, sensei.
It got hard, though.
I'm stroking it with my handsies.
Do you like it or not?
O-Of course, I like it but...
Stroke the dick up and down~!
Good boy, good boy~!
Let it out, sensei!
Feel good and make it spurt!
Ohh!
It's dripping out!
You see, when I smell this gooey stuff...
My tummy feels tight...
Hey...
I'm gonna clean you up.
Doesh it fweel good, sensei?
Ahh, it feels good...
It came out again...
Hey, we'll wake Tieru-san up. Let's sleep already.
Ehh! Just a bit more!
I certainly told you to have sex with my little sister!
But I never told you to do it right next to me!
You're right... I'm sorry...
By the way, don't you have to do it too?
You said it is an essential task for your race.
I-I have the duty of protecting my little sister!
I don't have to sleep with men...
Ehh!? Just ask sensei to do it with you too, onee-chan!
I'm sure you'll also end up liking him!
What!?
Come on, sensei! Let's show it to onee-chan!
What... Ehh!?
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji